<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" 
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" 
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <channel>
    <title>Corey Petty&#39;s Personal Website</title>
    <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Corey Petty&#39;s Personal Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</webMaster>
    <copyright>©2021, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://coreypetty.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    

      
      <item>
        <title>Is a Ledger hardware wallet succeptible to a &#34;retirement attack?&#34;</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/2020-11-01_ledger-retirement-attack/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/2020-11-01_ledger-retirement-attack/</guid>
        <description>Introduction After an interview with Toby Simpson, the COO of fetch.ai, on Hashing It Out (will be released shortly), I shared a blog article of his that was mentioned in The Bitcoin Podcast slack for others to read it. It is a post about the consequences of &amp;ldquo;becoming a bank&amp;rdquo; that aren&amp;rsquo;t often talked about, and gives some guidance on how to increase your level of personal security by setting up a hardware wallet.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>ledger</category>
            
          
            
              <category>hardware wallets</category>
            
          
            
              <category>security</category>
            
          
            
              <category>retirement attack</category>
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>blockchain</category>
            
          
            
              <category>explainer</category>
            
          
            
              <category>security</category>
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Schnorr and Taproot make it into Bitcoin codebase. So what?</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/2020-10-18_bitcoin-schnorr-taproot/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/2020-10-18_bitcoin-schnorr-taproot/</guid>
        <description>As per usual, folks were sending interesting news in he Bitcoin Podcast slack. This one happened to catch my eye as it&#39;s an update I&#39;ve been waiting for; Bitcoin is getting two major improvements in historic code update from Decrypt. I immediately said we would talk about this in the upcoming The Bitcoin Podcast episode roundtable. But first, I&#39;d wanted to take some notes and jot down a few things so that I can share what these technologies are, what they potentially mean, and the remaining road ahead for those that don&#39;t listen the podcast, but are still interested.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>taproot</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Bitcoin</category>
            
          
            
              <category>schnorr</category>
            
          
            
              <category>tapscript</category>
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>blockchain</category>
            
          
            
              <category>explainer</category>
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Understand What People Mean When They Say “We’re Probably in a Simulation.”</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/how-to-understand-what-people-mean-when-they-say-were-probably-in-a-simulation-f838bad0a92/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 03:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 03:42:57 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/how-to-understand-what-people-mean-when-they-say-were-probably-in-a-simulation-f838bad0a92/</guid>
        <description>I recently listened to an episode of Joe Rogan where Nick Bostrom tried to explain the concept of simulation theory. Although the progenitor of the concept tried multiple times, it seemed as though there was some roadblock to understanding, so I’d like to give it a shot. The best method would be to do it through the Socratic method, where questions are asked to allow the other participants to reach the conclusion desired themselves.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Reframing how you think about the concept of “managing your private keys”</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/reframing-how-you-think-about-the-concept-of-managing-your-private-keys-fdf95060728a/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 18:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 18:13:29 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/reframing-how-you-think-about-the-concept-of-managing-your-private-keys-fdf95060728a/</guid>
        <description>If you’ve been around the cryptocurrency community for long, then you’ve definitely heard people preach sayings such as, “Always remember to control your private keys.” Maybe it was through a commonly said aphorism:
 Your keys, your crypto; Not your keys, not your crypto.
 But what does it actually mean? If you don’t understand public-private key cryptography, then those sayings offer no explanation or insight to one of the most important features of this technology: controlling the access to your value.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Role of Randomness in Proof of Work Mining</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/the-role-of-randomness-in-proof-of-work-mining-3827a809f745/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 23:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 23:06:54 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/the-role-of-randomness-in-proof-of-work-mining-3827a809f745/</guid>
        <description>I hear people throw shade at idea of Proof of Stake (PoS) protocols quite often. I think that most of these comments are founded in false assumptions, which inevitably lead them to false conclusions. That’s a deep amount of work, which requires some groundwork first. This is some groundwork, so this is about abstracting away some of the roles Proof of Work (PoW) plays in blockchain protocols, and looking at how randomness is at the heart of them, and where that randomness comes from.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Petty Crypto Review: Cardano</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/a-petty-crypto-review-cardano-a2c99fd413af/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 01:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 01:54:31 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/a-petty-crypto-review-cardano-a2c99fd413af/</guid>
        <description>So I get hit up quite frequently about various coins and whether or not they’re worth looking into, are a scam, are legit, etc. So I’ve decided to try and pick some of the coins I get asked about most that I don’t already know about, and read a bit about them, and give some off-the-cuff opinions on their validity to refer my friends and family to. I hope others find these useful.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Getting Past the Golden Hammer with a Quantum Mechanics Example: A Valuable Lesson for Blockchain</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/getting-past-the-golden-hammer-with-a-quantum-mechanics-example-a-valuable-lesson-for-blockchain-f254c289dad0/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 20:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 20:55:31 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/getting-past-the-golden-hammer-with-a-quantum-mechanics-example-a-valuable-lesson-for-blockchain-f254c289dad0/</guid>
        <description>When reading about Bitcoin, Ethereum, Blockchain, other alt coins, etc… (I’ll use capital B — Blockchain here to encompass them all) I hear a lot of people say something akin to the following:
 Blockchain can’t be good at everything, it has to choose one thing and be the best at it, and that should be &amp;lt;insert your idea here&amp;gt;.
 Hell, I’m guilty of saying things like this myself, which is partly why I’m writing this.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Merkle-ization of Individuality</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/the-merkle-ization-of-individuality-e53618de835d/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 23:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 23:03:33 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/the-merkle-ization-of-individuality-e53618de835d/</guid>
        <description>Unlike most of my posts or writings, this is not a technical one. It borrows from the technical world a bit, but its purpose is more of a social endeavor.
I’ve always had this amorphous construction in my head that I’ve used to think about what makes a person who they are. Why do they make the decisions they make and what makes them tick? I’m sure you’ve heard the term “everyone is a unique snowflake” or some form of that mentality.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Look at the Status.im ICO Token Distribution</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/a-look-at-the-status-im-ico-token-distribution-f5bcf7f00907/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 03:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 03:47:04 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/a-look-at-the-status-im-ico-token-distribution-f5bcf7f00907/</guid>
        <description>NOTE UP FRONT: I express my opinions here (at least at the end of the article). If you don’t like them and don’t have evidence to support your dislike, then go kick rocks.
Things are moving forward quite rapidly in this space; I simply don’t have time to look at all the ICOs (ya know, full time job, podcast, wife, and stuff), but this one struck me as different while also being wildly anticipated.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Look at the BAT Token Distribution</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/a-look-at-the-bat-token-distribution-bb3bcb92748f/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 01:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 01:35:25 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/a-look-at-the-bat-token-distribution-bb3bcb92748f/</guid>
        <description>Jesus H. Christ folks. I’ve put off doing this one a little bit, in part because I’m a bit depressed/disappointed/confused/? in the direction this is headed. As always, I’ll leave my opinions until the end, so those of you who are strictly reading for the data herein can click “close” when I start ranting.
The Basic Attention Token ICO, lead by Brendan Eich, is an attempt to tokenize human attention on the internet.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Look at the Aragon ICO Investment Distribution</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/a-look-at-the-aragon-ico-investment-distribution-a78f601229d8/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 17:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Thu, 18 May 2017 17:45:33 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/a-look-at-the-aragon-ico-investment-distribution-a78f601229d8/</guid>
        <description>Another ERC20 Initial Coin Offering (ICO), another ridiculous amount of money, in another ridiculously short period of time. This time around, it’s with the Aragon Project, a play at making “unstoppable organizations on the blockchain.”
Not gonna lie, I played with their Alpha release, and enjoyed it. It has potential to do some cool stuff. The goal of this article is not to critique the platform, but only to look at the distribution of Ethereum ICOs to help people see the trends of the space.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Look at the TokenCard ICO Investor Distribution</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/a-look-at-the-tokencard-ico-investor-distribution-cddeb6f534f9/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 22:44:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Tue, 02 May 2017 22:44:57 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/a-look-at-the-tokencard-ico-investor-distribution-cddeb6f534f9/</guid>
        <description>This is another look at the distribution of an ICO in the Ethereum space, because I think its important to see the overall trends of how these projects are getting funded so we can draw rational conclusions from evidence, instead of just saying stuff that we feel without any real backing.
What’s TokenCard? Monolith Studio’s TokenCard is a platform to hold your ERC20 tokens, as well as spend them using a visa debit card.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Look at the Gnosis Dutch Auction Distribution</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/a-look-at-the-gnosis-dutch-auction-distribution-25c2ccac2d9d/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 20:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 20:33:57 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/a-look-at-the-gnosis-dutch-auction-distribution-25c2ccac2d9d/</guid>
        <description>Edit: I changed Gnosis’ front page $300 extrapolated number to 250k ETH at $50/ETH = $12.5 Mil for clarity and self containment.
Alright, so the Gnosis dutch auction reached their goal of 250K ETH in less than 15 minutes. I’m not too terribly surprised, to be honest, it was an incredibly popular project in the space.
$12.5 million in less than 15 minutes…
I was too late, because I was fiddling around with other things, like my job.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A layman’s line-by-line description of Gavin’s Preliminary hard-fork code</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/a-laymens-line-by-line-description-of-gavin-s-preliminary-hard-fork-code-6daa8c5c1a30/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2016 17:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Wed, 29 Jun 2016 17:08:25 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/a-laymens-line-by-line-description-of-gavin-s-preliminary-hard-fork-code-6daa8c5c1a30/</guid>
        <description>Here I will attempt to perform a line-by-line description of Gavin’s recent preliminary hard-fork code submitted to github, which can be found here. I am not a Rust coder, but I have experience with low-level programming languages (Fortran, C), and high-level scripting languages (Python, R, Bash), so I feel I have a pretty good idea what’s going on.
It is important that everyone understand what the code is doing, regardless of whether or not they can read code.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The DAO: What happened, Who did it, Where do we go?</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/the-dao-what-happened-who-did-it-where-do-we-go-4897d7864e/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 02:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 02:09:37 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/the-dao-what-happened-who-did-it-where-do-we-go-4897d7864e/</guid>
        <description>It’s clear something tremendous has happened to the cryptocurrency environment, and it’s not the good kind of something. You’re about to be inundated with a large amount of coverage about all things crypto from many sources, and a lot of it will probably be garbage.
 An opinion is only worth the facts that are used to form it.
 In other words, if nothing concrete is backing the things coming out of your mouth, then you’re spewing bullshit, and your opinion doesn’t matter.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Our #dao_data channel on the slack has a current list of known exchange addresses.</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/our-dao-data-channel-on-the-slack-has-a-current-list-of-known-exchange-addresses-f50b42c034e5/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 15:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 15:34:32 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/our-dao-data-channel-on-the-slack-has-a-current-list-of-known-exchange-addresses-f50b42c034e5/</guid>
        <description>Our #dao_data channel on the slack has a current list of known exchange addresses.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Don’t cling to past ideas so tight to try and explain the future</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/if-what-you-do-transcends-the-archetypes-of-its-predecessors-then-yes-you-can-f86298b658a1/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Tue, 24 May 2016 22:24:00 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/if-what-you-do-transcends-the-archetypes-of-its-predecessors-then-yes-you-can-f86298b658a1/</guid>
        <description>If what you do transcends the archetypes of its predecessors, then it can become something not explainable by them.
When quantum mechanics was formulated, people argued light cannot be both a wave and a particle at the same time. They were right, and wrong, it is neither. It is something that can’t be explained through the old frameworks of “waves” and “particles” because what light is transcends them both.
Cryptocurrencies are poised to potentially do the same, if we try to free ourselves from looking only through the lens of old archetypes.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Looking at the DAO Token Distribution: Part 2</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/looking-at-the-dao-token-distribution-part-2-c77e7c4ac81c/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 02:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Tue, 24 May 2016 02:16:21 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/looking-at-the-dao-token-distribution-part-2-c77e7c4ac81c/</guid>
        <description>Well boys and girls, we’ve done some things. If you’ve invested into The DAO, welcome to the largest crowdfunded/kickstarter/other “traditional analogy that doesn’t quite cut it” in history. The truth is, we’ve done something historical, and possibly game changing and foundational to how organizations pool and spend money (among other things). Let’s take some more time to look at who has invested, and how much has been put in, to see if we can draw some conclusions</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Great general overview of the current state of Ethereum.</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/great-general-overview-of-the-current-state-of-ethereum-833aebe08612/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 17:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Mon, 23 May 2016 17:05:46 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/great-general-overview-of-the-current-state-of-ethereum-833aebe08612/</guid>
        <description>Great general overview of the current state of Ethereum. This just became my go-to source to help people who may be curious get a sense of where things are. Thank you for taking your time and creating this.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Looking at the DAO address distribution: Part 1</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/looking-at-the-dao-address-distribution-part-1-f324e71381bf/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 14:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Tue, 17 May 2016 14:35:59 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/looking-at-the-dao-address-distribution-part-1-f324e71381bf/</guid>
        <description>So the first purchase ratio of The DAO creation phase is over. Gone are the days you can get the 100 DAO Tokens for 1 ETH. Due to the relatively high difficulty in understanding what The DAO actually is, and how to actually invest in it, I think that the majority of the potential investors have already “gone in.” I could be wrong, but either way, I think an analysis of the token distribution up to this point is in order.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Bitcoin Market Cap and Mining Decentralization</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/we-got-an-interesting-question-on-one-of-our-latest-episodes-on-the-topic-of-mining-and-how-the-dc475ab79bea/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 17:20:00 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/we-got-an-interesting-question-on-one-of-our-latest-episodes-on-the-topic-of-mining-and-how-the-dc475ab79bea/</guid>
        <description>We got an interesting question on one of our latest episodes on the topic of mining and how the market cap could effect it.
 Enjoyed the show guys,
  Thinking about mining and the price of bitcoin and decentralization… Do you guys think that an increase in the price of bitcoin, i.e. 1trillion market cap, or more, would have a negative effect on mining? To the point that it would not be worth it for big miners to mine because the resources put into operation do not correlate to greater returns.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Bitcoin as a Vehicle for Personal Growth</title>
        <link>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/bitcoin-as-a-vehicle-for-personal-growth-ee0f3ebbed43/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 00:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>corey@petty.services (Corey Petty, PhD)</author>
        <atom:modified>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 00:15:22 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://coreypetty.com/posts/medium/corpetty/bitcoin-as-a-vehicle-for-personal-growth-ee0f3ebbed43/</guid>
        <description>Note: This is a copy-over from our website’s blog, which we are transfering over to this platform. It was originally published 7 months ago, and hosted on http://thebitcoinpodcast.com/bitcoin-as-a-vehicle-for-personal-growth/
There seems to be a problem here
Often times when talking with people about Bitcoin, I get a lot of questions about safety and security. This usually leads to a discussion culminating with the questioner’s realization of their own ignorance of how money actually works.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>Corey Petty, PhD</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      

    
  </channel>
</rss>
